lanmeiairlines.com 2018-12-12

# Privacy clause

## 1\. Privacy commitment

Lanmei Airlines Limited (hereinafter referred to as "Lanmei") understands that your privacy is important and ensures as far as possible that personal information collected through this web site is used only for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

## 2\. Introduction

1)This Privacy Policy explains Lanmei’s policies in relation to the handling of personal information that maybe collected on this web site.

2)By using this web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Lanmei. This only applies to the extent that consent given in this way is legally effective.

## 3\. Information on the Lanmei Privacy Policy covers the following areas:

1)Information We Collect And How We Collect It

2)How Your Information Will Be Used

3)Where We Store Your Data

4)Links To Other Sites

5)Your Rights

6)Cookies And Web Beacons

7)API (Advanced Passenger Information)

8)Data Security

9)Contacting Us

10)Access to Information

11)Privacy Modifications

## 4\. Information We Collect And How We Collect It

In order to facilitate your travel, and manage our business, we collect and maintain personal information about you. Lanmei collects customer information from many sources to understand and meet your needs. We collect personal information about you from: 

1)You, when you voluntarily provide us with information; 

2)Your browser, when you visit our websites and your browser interacts with us; 

3)Your transactions with the Lanmei web site ;

4)Other sources, including Lanmei travel partner web sites (for example, hotel partners, car rental partners and tour company partners), in connection with providing your transportation needs and services.

## 5\. The personal information we collect about you through these various sources may include:

1)Name, addresses and telephone numbers

2)Email addresses, fax numbers and pager numbers

3)Companion frequent flyer program account number and flight information

4)Online forms of payment like credit card number(s), including associated billing address(es) and expiration date(s)

5)Information necessary to facilitate travel or other services, including travel companion(s) names,emergency contacts, special service needs.

6)Passport number, nationality and country of residence

7)Use of products and services such as self-service devices, flight status notification and web check-in

8)Personal information provided via survey, focus group or other marketing research efforts

9)Personal information provided to customer-service representatives to research and resolve issues or questions

10)Corporate-contract, employer and/or other corporate affiliation (i.e. employer name, title, address and contact information)

## 6\. We share this information within the Lanmei group companies (which means Lanmei and its subsidiaries) and with our third party suppliers for the purposes as outlined below only. 

1)Aggregate information

In addition to obtaining your personal information, when you use our site, we may collect tracking information such as your browser type, the type of operating system you use, the name of your Internet service provider, and pages visited on our site. Lanmei gets this information by using technologies, including cookies and web beacons, to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our site and to better tailor our site, products, and services to our visitors’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors meet the criteria required to process their requests and for reporting onsite activity in the aggregate. For further information on cookies and web beacons, and how you may elect to reject them, please refer to the section "Cookies and Web Beacons" below.

2)Children

As we cannot distinguish the age of persons who access our web site, a blanket privacy policy is applied. If a child has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should email us at lm-ec@lanmeiairlines.com to remove the information or unsubscribe from any promotional contact opportunities. Lanmei does not intend to or seek to receive information from minors.

## 7\. How Your Information Will Be Used

1)Lanmei uses personally identifiable information to complete transactions and fulfill requests for our services. Lanmei requires you to provide personal information when making a reservation to purchase airline tickets or ancillary travel products and services on this web site, or enrolling in the Companion program. In addition to processing, confirming and fulfilling the travel or other services you request, Lanmei may use these data for administrative and analytical purposes such as accounting, billing and audits, marketing, credit card processing and verification, customer-relations correspondence and information systems management in relation to the aforementioned.

2)To the extent required by applicable law, we may disclose personally identifiable information to government authorities, or to third parties pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process, and we may also use or disclose your information as permitted by law to protect the rights or property of Lanmei, our customers, our website, or its users.

3)Lanmei does not sell any customer information or share your email address with any third parties except in compliance with this policy. However, we may disclose customer information to companies affiliated with Lanmei and/or unaffiliated third parties to fulfill supply of the products and services you have requested. We may also disclose this information to third parties, such as employers, who have arranged for discounts, purchased travel or other services on your behalf, but only to the extent it is necessary for them to know such information. Additionally, Lanmei may combine the information we receive from you with information collected from other sources. This information would be used to provide offers and/or services specifically tailored to your interests. We will not use any data regarding your surfing behaviour for marketing purposes (except on an anonymous basis) without first obtaining your explicit consent.

4)If we sell a business unit to another company and your personal data is used by that business unit then your data may be transferred to the buyer along with the business for them to use in the same way. We will not transfer the data if this is contrary to law.

Please indicate you consent to your data being used as described in this section "How Your Information Will Be Used" by ticking the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

## 8\. Where We Store Your Data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the Cambodia(for the purpose of this Privacy Policy). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the People’s Republic of China who work for any company within the Lanmei group or for one of our third party suppliers. These staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your booking, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.

By providing your data, you agree to the transfer, storing or processing of your personal data as described herein.

## 9\. Links To Other Sites

Lanmei uses links to other Internet sites to improve your experience of our website. We will always seek to make these links clear by opening them in a new window of your web browser. However, please be aware that these websites may be owned and run by other companies and organizations. Lanmei does not endorse any such websites and we are not responsible for the information, material, products or services contained on or accessible through those websites. Your access and use of such websites remains solely at your own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for any information you divulge to a linked website.

Please note that the Lanmei Privacy Policy does not cover these other websites, and Lanmei would recommend that you are apprised of their specific policies. 

## 10\. Your Rights

1)If you have explicitly consented through our web site, we will, from time to time, use your data to deliver materials about products or services of Lanmei (and other selected third parties, including Lanmei ancillary travel and promotion partners) which may be of interest to you by e-mail. You have the right to ask us not to process your data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to inform us by e-mailing lm-ec@lanmeiairlines.com at any time to stop using your data for marketing purposes.

2)For the avoidance of doubt, you may at any time object to our use of your data by sending an email to lm-ec@lanmeiairlines.com.

3)If you are an existing Lanmei customer, we will only contact you by e-mail with materials about products or services similar to those which have been previously provided to you (unless you consent to receiving e-mails about other products or services by ticking the relevant box situated on the form when we collect your data).

4)If you are a new customer, and where we permit certain third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by e-mail only if you have consented to this. We (or they) will contact you for the purposes of informing you about our (their) company news, products and services. Please indicate your consent to being contacted by e-mail by ticking the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

## 11\. Cookies And Web Beacons

1)A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. Cookies will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. Two types of cookies are used on this website - session cookies, which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site, and persistent cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie). Most browsers have options that allow the visitor to control whether the browser will accept cookies, reject cookies, or notify the visitor each time a cookie is sent. You may elect to reject cookies by adjusting your browser's settings, but doing so will limit the range of features available to the visitor on our site and most other major websites that use cookies. To find out more information about cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

2)Web beacons are used in conjunction with cookies to record the simple actions of the user opening the page that contains the beacon. When a user's browser requests information from a website in this way certain simple information can also be gathered, such as: the IP address of your computer; time the material was viewed; the type of browser that retrieved the image; and the existence of cookies previously set by that server. This is information that is available to any web server you visit. Web beacons do not give any "extra" information away. They are simply a convenient way of gathering the simplest of statistics and managing cookies.

## 12\. API (Advanced Passenger Information) 

1)A growing number of destination countries oblige the airlines that fly to them to transmit passenger data before an aircraft lands in one of them. Usually, these legal regulations encompass the transmission of data on the passengers' identity and travel documents (passport, visa).

2)As a rule, an airline does not have these data, so it must collect them shortly before an aircraft departs, which increasingly is being done by means of the so-called 'machine-readable zone' in the new travel documents. If we are requested to transmit your passenger data to authorities other than the People’s Republic of China (for the purpose of this Privacy Policy, it shall not include Hong Kong SPR, Macau SPR and Taiwan Province), we will obtain your consent before doing so.

3)Collection of the data is done solely for immediate transmission to the authorities of the destination country.

## 13\. Data Security

Lanmei a takes your data security very seriously. In addition to complying with all applicable data security regulations, to ensure the highest possible security for the transmission of your data between your web browser and our internet system we use the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypting technology. SSL is an industry standard way to send personal information over the Internet. It enables an encrypted communication respectively transfer of documents via the internet between web browser and web server. The URL of a website with SSL connection to your browser starts with https://. SSL is fast, secure, and it ensures that your personal information will not be read by anyone else.

## 14\. Contacting Us

If there is any doubts, suggestion or opinion about our Privacy Policy, please contact E-commerce Department of Lanmei Airlines by emailing lm-ec@lanmeiairlines.com and mark “Private Policy”.

## 15\. Access to Information

You may logon on our website at any time checking and modifying any of your information including name, address, phone number or email address to ensure the accuracy of your personal information. No others have the right to modify or delete the information you provide, except in the event that you disclose your account number, pass code to the others or that your personal information is lost, stolen or juggled due to hacker attack, computer virus, and other force majeure events which cannot be controlled during normal Internet operation. If you intend to modify or delete any of your information, please send your written request to lm-ec@lanmeiairlines.com.

## 16\. Privacy Modification

Lanmei Airlines reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and the updated versions will be posted on our website and date stamped so that you are aware of when the Privacy Policy was last updated.
